[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
[Sung Inho]
[Kim Domin]
[Summertime]
I like you.
Will it make you feel better
to pretend everything I do
is just a joke?
You know my feelings for you.
Don't you?
You weren't sleeping
in the classroom that day.
You jerk.
Are you okay?
Hey. I heard Eunho got into an accident.
What? You saw it?
I saw him in the nurse's office.
He was covered in blood.
Why are you running in the hallway
in the morning...
Dohyun...
Mom and Dad...
What are we going to do now?
Whether it's taekwondo or studying—
nothing's easy.
But Yeo Eunho...
you're really hard to understand.
So...
there must be another way, you jerk.
If I don't do this,
can you see my feelings for you?
Yeo Eunho. Just give it to me straight.
What?
If you don't like me, just say so.
If you say you don't like me,
I'll never do anything
that crosses the line again.
-Cheers!
Drink up.
It's so darn good.
Hey, do you have water?
It was so hard for me to bring this.
You have to drink it.
You should've bought water.
Drink the alcohol.
I said to drink this instead of soju.
Go get some water!
You scared me!
Eunho!
Do you see this?
21 years—it's a 21-year alcohol.
It's super expensive!
Eunho, just go.
Why?
If that darn Cha Dohyun finds out,
we'll be—
Hey. All you have to do is say nothing.
You were the tattletale.
I'm not—
why are you so rude today?
Yeah, Eunho.
You don't drink anyway.
-I drink.
-What?
You drink? Since when?
Since now.
Since we have a new guest,
he should have a drink.
Give it to him.
Are you sure?
Are you that scared of him?
I'm just worried about you.
You coward.
Cheers.
-Cheers!
-Eunho, pass me the glass.
-You're quite good at drinking.
It's empty.
You walk in,
but you have to crawl out.
You and Gunwoo need to get drunk
to get out.
Got it?
Let's get drunk.
[Cha Dohyun]
Hey.
Who was the person
holding your hand last night?
Gosh! Who was it?
-Me?
-Yeah.
Someone saw you coming out of the karaoke.
At 1:05 a.m.
Hey, I heard about it too.
What are you talking about?
Look at him being all shy.
Hey! Did you kiss?
Crazy bastard.
Not yet!
Not yet?
Tell me an alphabet and number you like.
H, 2.
That's...
Crazy bastard.
That's enough.
You've never kissed, have you?
-What are you doing?
-Get lost!
Get lost!
Why are you just sitting here?
[Cha Dohyon]
Cha Dohyun?
That tall and handsome guy?
Give it back.
Amazing! Are you close to him?
Give it back!
Hello?
Are you crazy?
Damn, I almost got you.
Does he have a girlfriend?
No.
Oh, my. Then introduce him to me.
Why?
He doesn't have a girlfriend, right?
He has someone he likes.
I'm leaving.
What's wrong?
Where are you going so early?
Then give me his number.
I have to go.
Give me his number.
Just his number.
Oh, my. It's Cha Dohyun.
Why did you make someone studying
run over here like a crazy dog?
You really can make me
look like an idiot easily.
Hey, you come out too.
Quick!
You're funny.
Making me so annoyed.
Do you find it funny
hearing me say I like you.
Is this your answer?
I got it, Yeo Eunho.
Cha Dohyun.
Can you really not see me forever?
Yes.
Do you think
I'll be scared by that threat?
Ridiculous.
Honey, wake up.
Yeo Eunho! Time for school!
Gosh, you're ready already?
I'm going to school.
What about breakfast?
I'm not hungry.
You forgot your bag.
Why are you playing with your phone
so early in the morning?
I'm going to school.
Hey, are you okay?
[No new notifications]
-Name tags.
-Yes.
Remember to check
if they have their name tags on.
Also, catch students
who aren't buttoned up.
Check if their tie is on too.
Okay.
[Yeo Eunho]
Eunho, you're early.
Hey, your slippers.
I guess this is the trend these days.
Why didn't you tell me?
I can't miss out on the trend.
This is not bad.
Hey, Eunho.
Huh?
What's up? You've been out of it.
If it goes in, it means I like him.
If it doesn't...
then I don't.
If it doesn't go in,
then I don't like him.
Darn it.
You jerk.
You didn't bring an umbrella?
Yeah.
The weather forecast
didn't say it was going to rain.
Thunder showers happen all of a sudden.
It's normal that it wasn't forecasted.
Do you want to share an umbrella?
No.
I'll leave after the rain stops.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
Cha Dohyun...
Come out, Cha Dohyun.
I'm cold, so come out immediately.
Yeo Eunho.
Can you really not see me forever?
Cha Dohyun.
I think I'm done for.
[Summertime]
I like you.
I'm not going to be friends
with you anymore.
I want to date you.
Are you crazy?
Are you crazy? We're in school.
Yeo Eunho.
Do you want to come to my house now?
You pervert. I'm hanging up.
If you don't come, I'll go to you.
Are you okay with anything?
Is there nothing you want to do?
You said you were childhood friends.
How long do you think
this friendship will last?
Going to different universities,
doing different jobs—
you'll have to grow up one day.
Friends or not,
people will hang out with people
they're more alike with.
Yes.
Eunho, what's wrong?